so you're coming off testosterone cream
and you're trying to Kickstart your
endocrine system utilizing an LH analog
which is HCG and then a selective
estrogen receptor modulator which is
tamoxifen no one can answer the question
for you because we don't know what your
initial diagnosis was if your initial
diagnosis was primary hypogonadism or
testicular hypo function then coming off
trt is never going to replace your
natural production sufficiently
basically your testicular function was
diminished over the course of your
lifespan whether it's due to acute
injury or re or you know it could have
been a a slow decline over the course of
time either way if your testicular
function has diminished then trying to
come off and letting your body naturally
replace it as a mood point it's just
never going to happen if your issue was
secondary which is a pituitary or
hypothalamic problem than restarting
that Loop May and I say may with an
asterisk because often times it fails
but it may work for you my question is
why do you want to come off and why do
you want to you know go back to a state
where presumably you were previously
deprived of optimal levels now my guys
shouldn't come off because my guys are
started on therapy because they are
deficient we don't start guys who are
just curious and want a little pump for
the gym um we start guys who have a
medical necessity so if you started for
the right reasons you should not be
coming off testosterone if you started
for the wrong reasons then you know
again we don't have your initial
assessment to be able to diagnose and or
put together a plan of action as to
dosing and frequency I don't know your
age I don't know your medical history we
can't what we can do is we can give a
blanket statement that is based on
scientific evidence what we cannot do in
these video sessions is give specific
medical advice to individuals based on
their needs because that does require a
proper assessment and anyone that's
going to come on here and just say
here's your dose here's your frequency
here's what you should be doing outside
of being highly legal it is unethical
and it is just morally wrong to advise
someone you know nothing about
[Music]